axiscam.net 2006-07-11

# Axis Communications - Privacy policy

Axis online privacy policy 

Axis and its subsidiaries are committed to protecting your online privacy. We have designed our Web sites in a way that will enable you to visit and access most of the available information and material without having to submit any personal data unless you choose to. 

By accessing or using an Axis Web site, you agree to the terms of the Axis online privacy policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. Axis reserves the right to change the online privacy policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the online privacy policy at the time of such use. 

Purpose

Personally identifiable information that you choose to submit to us or that we collect is used solely for the purpose of improving relations between you and Axis. We are posting Axis' privacy policy online to clearly explain our intentions and create a sound basis for a mutual relationship. 

What we collect and why

We collect information mostly about what interests you on our Web site. For instance, if you take an interest in our newsletters, we will require your e-mail address. Sometimes we use a technology involving cookies, which can, for instance, help make your browsing experience simpler. (You can read more about how we use cookies below.) 

We use the information you choose to submit to us to support our mutual relationship, to understand your needs and to improve our support for your needs. We can use the information to improve our offers and services to you, by helping you stay informed of new software versions, for instance. 

In addition to information you submit to us we also log which pages are accessed in order to improve our site for ease of use and other purposes. 

Credit card numbers that you enter are never saved. They are only kept during the transaction and validation process. This may be done using a third party clearing house. 

Market contact

On occasion we may contact you to provide you with market information that we believe is of interest to you, or we may ask for your opinions in a market survey. We may also notify you of your ability to subscribe to a number of newsletters that provide, for example, up-to-date information on our current products or solutions. You will always have the option of telling us whether or not you want to receive such market information or be involved in our research activities. 

Sharing information

Axis will not sell, trade or lease to third parties personally identifiable information that you provide to us. Unless we have informed you otherwise and have obtained your permission, or the law forces us to, we will only use the collected information within Axis or with business partners that act on our behalf. 

As stated previously, you have the option of letting us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials, and we will strive to honor your request. 

Information integrity

Axis strives to keep your personally identifiable information correct. We will make every effort to have your personal data available to you for viewing, or for making corrections or additions. To protect your information, we use a personal security login system to verify your identity before allowing you access to your data. Furthermore, we employ physical and electronic protection mechanisms to secure access and to protect the data from unauthorized access. 

Links to other sites

Sometimes you will find links to third party sites on our Web pages. Please note that this online privacy policy does not automatically apply to these third party sites. 

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of text that a Web site can store on your computer to enable it to recognize you when you return to the site. At Axis, we first ask for your permission to store cookies on your computer. Cookies help us to analyze visiting patterns on our Web site. It also helps us support customer relations by enabling us, for instance, to simplify your login procedure when you want to download software upgrades. Sometimes we use cookies to make your browsing experience easier or to enable us to make Web site usage analysis on an aggregated level (i.e. on a non-personal, collective manner for the purpose of tracking overall movements and visits to certain pages on our Web site, for example). 

If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact us.
